{
    "subject": "resource/A_Lowland_Cinderella",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:British_films",
    "human_readable": "A Lowland Cinderella is about British films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9448272585868835,
            "question": "Does 'A Lowland Cinderella' discuss both British and international films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9252856969833374,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a specific British film that might be mentioned in 'A Lowland Cinderella'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.781609296798706,
            "question": "Is 'A Lowland Cinderella' a novel or a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.636449933052063,
            "question": "What type of films does the book 'A Lowland Cinderella' focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6002979278564453,
            "question": "What historical period are the films discussed in 'A Lowland Cinderella' likely to cover?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5434167385101318,
            "question": "What is the subject of the book 'A Lowland Cinderella'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47873830795288086,
            "question": "Who is the author of 'A Lowland Cinderella'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4291858673095703,
            "question": "What genre might 'A Lowland Cinderella' fall into?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26094475388526917,
            "question": "Why would someone be interested in reading 'A Lowland Cinderella'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19378815591335297,
            "question": "Are there any other books similar to 'A Lowland Cinderella' that you can recommend?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A Lowland Cinderella is about British films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4717_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why would someone be interested in reading 'A Lowland Cinderella'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4717_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might 'A Lowland Cinderella' fall into?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4717_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the author of 'A Lowland Cinderella'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4717_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4717_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that \"A Lowland Cinderella\" (1921) was one of Britain's first feature films and was made by Progress in the Shoreham \u2018Glasshouse\u2019 studio, indicating it is indeed about British cinema."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "'A Lowland Cinderella' is a British film adaptation of a Scottish novel, but its production location was not in Scotland but on the English south coast.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}